Guide to the Lois Gould Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Other Papers, 1940-2002; Series V; 5; (5 boxes)
  - Passports and identification cards, 1952, undated (Box 28, Folder 535)
  - Writing for school, undated (Box 28, Folder 536)
  - Correspondence and photographs, undated (Box 28, Folder 537)
  - Personal financial papers, 1970-1973, undated (Box 29, Folder 538-542)
  - Kennel Club documents, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 543)
  - "Lois Gould: A Tribute", 2002 (Box 29, Folder 544)
  - Mary Curzon Project, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 545)
  - "Girl With Tiara" proposals, notes, correspondence, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 546-547)
  - "Women Heroes of Ireland," drafts and research materials, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 548)
- Oversize, 0.75; (3 boxes)
  - Articles, printed versions (Series I.), 1971-1978 (Box 30, Folder 549-552)
  - Articles, printed versions (Series I.), 1971-1978 (Box 31, Folder 553-556)
  - La Presidenta, Galley Proofs (Series I.), circa 1981 (Box 34, Folder 559-562)
- Restricted Fragile, 0.42; (2 boxes)
  - Computer disk (Series III.) (Box 32, Folder 557)
    Box 32 (original computer disk): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - CBC-FM Network Ideas, "Pornography and Romance," Program 4, reel-to-reel audiotape (Series V.) (Box 33, Folder 558)
    Box 33 (reel-to-reel tape): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.